Peter Wexler papers 1965 - ongoing
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Papers., Series:I
  - Photography. Wexler History. Photos Not by Peter Wexler. General Sleigh. 1956-1958 (Box 134)
  - Photography. Wexler History. Photos Not by Peter Wexler. General The Grass Beach. 1956-1958 (Box 134)
  - Photography. Wexler History. Photos Not by Peter Wexler. “To God” Trees Branches and Leaves. 1956-1958 (Box 134)
  - Photography. Wexler History. Photos Not by Peter Wexler. Sheep Farm Tree Branches. 1956-1958 (Box 134)
  - Photography. Wexler History. Photos Not by Peter Wexler. Portraits Various. 1956-1958 (Box 134)
  - Photography. Wexler History. Photos Not by Peter Wexler. Portraits Bea Minkus. 1956-1958 (Box 134)
  - Photography. Wexler History. Photos Not by Peter Wexler. Essay- Faces in the Crowd. 1956-1958 (Box 134)
  - Photography. Wexler History. Photos Not by Peter Wexler. Essay- Saturday’s Business Man 2 of 2. 1956-1958 (Box 134)
  - Photography. Wexler History. Photos Not by Peter Wexler. Essay- Saturday’s Business Man 1 of 2. 1956-1958 (Box 134)
  - Photography. Wexler History. Photos Not by Peter Wexler. Essay- Pigeons in Cornices. 1956-1958 (Box 134)
  - Photography. Wexler History. Photos Not by Peter Wexler. Essay- On Fashion. 1956-1958 (Box 134)
  - Past Contracts. 1963-1993 (Box 135)
  - Past Contracts. 1-436. (1963-1980) 1963-1993 (Box 135)
  - Un Ballo In Maschera. 1980 (Box 135)
  - Un Ballo In Maschera. Sound Film Strip. 1980 (Box 135)
  - Un Ballo In Maschera. Audio Tapes and Record Album. 1980 (Box 135)
  - Publications. Various. 1980 (Box 135)
  - 437-982. (1979-1988) 1979-1988 (Box 136)
  - 983-1171. (1986-1993) 1986-1993 (Box 136)
  - Examples of Successful Proposals. Assorted Dates. (Box 137)
  - US Navy. Final Storyboards. 6/17/87. 1987 (Box 137)
  - Search for Life. Proposal Book. 1985 (Box 137)
  - Radio City Music Hall Productions New Pier 84. Proposal Book. 1989 (Box 137)
  - New York City Transit Authority. Proposal Books. 1991 (Box 137)
  - National Archives and Records Programs. 1989 (Box 137)
  - National Archives and Records Programs. WWII Design Concept “We’re All in This Together Proposal Book. 1989 (Box 137)
  - Publication: “Celebration- The Metropolitan Opera” By Francis Robinson. 1989 (Box 137)
  - Lifetime Medical Television. Presentation Book. 1990 (Box 137)
  - Library of Congress- Treasures of the Vatican. Proposal Books. 1992 (Box 137)
- Artwork., Series: II
  Arrangement: Chronological. Then under by title. Consult later box listings for projects added to the collection out of sequence.
  Location: Flat files.
  Quantity: 172 Linear feet.
  Description: Contains floor plans, elevations,and designs for: architecture, concerts, film, opera, public spaces,restaurant, television, and theatre.
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades. Theatre Design. 1965 (Map-case 1)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades. Theatre Design, Music. 1966 (Map-case 1)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades. Theatre Design, Music. 1967 (Map-case 1)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades. Theatre Design, Music. 1968 (Map-case 2)
  - Camino Real. Los Angeles. Theatre Design. 1968 (Map-case 2)
  - New York Philharmonic. Scriabin. Prometheus. Theatre Design, Music. 1969 (Map-case 3)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades. Theatre Design, Music. 1969 (Map-case 3)
  - Center Theatre Group. New Theatre for Now. USIA Tour. Theatre Design. 1969 (Map-case 3)
  - Center Theatre Group. Murderous Angels. Theatre Design. 1970 (Map-case 4)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades. Theatre Design, Music. 1970 (Map-case 4)
  - Apartment for Michael Bennett. Architectural. 1970 (Map-case 4)
  - Olympia Theatre Project. New York City. Architectural. 1970 (Map-case 4)
  - Minnies Boys. Theatre Design. 1970 (Map-case 4)
  - Camino Real. Lincoln Center. Theatre Design. 1970 (Map-case 4)
  - The Trial of Abraham Lincoln. Theatre Design. 1971 (Map-case 5)
  - Davidson Pool. Architectural. 1971 (Map-case 5)
  - A Sculpture Called Park. Arlan Realty. Architectural. 1971 (Map-case 5)
  - Street Cart for New York Food Vending. Brody Corporation. Restaurant Design. 1971 (Map-case 5)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades. Theatre Design, Music. 1971 (Map-case 5)
  - The Trial of the Catonsville Nine. Film. 1971 (Map-case 5)
  - The Trial of the Catonsville Nine. New York. Theatre Design, Stage. 1971 (Map-case 5)
  - The Gershwin Years. Philharmonic Hall. Lighting Design. 1971 (Map-case 5)
  - Murderous Angels. Phoenix Theatre. Theatre Design. 1971 (Map-case 5)
  - Godspell. Original show design. Theatre Design. 1971 (Map-case 5)
  - The Web and the Rock. Theatre Design. 1972 (Map-case 6)
  - Couch for Mr. and Mrs. Yogi Cohen, Other. 1972 (Map-case 6)
  - Cerlew River. Theatre Design. 1972 (Map-case 6)
  - Happy Talk. Theatre Design. Light Plot. Ground Plan Detail Drawing. 1972 (Map-case 6)
  - Lorrie. Theatre Design. Plan. Elevations. Detail Drawings. Original Copies. 1972 (Map-case 6)
  - Leonard Bernstein’s Mass. Theatre Design. Music. roughs & finals; roughs are slightly torn. 1972 (Map-case 6)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades. Theatre Design, Music. 1972 (Map-case 6)
  - Review of Reviews. Theatre Design, Music. 1973 (Map-case 6)
  - Stage B. Theatre Design. 1973 (Map-case 6)
  - New York Philharmonic. Rug Concerts and Promenades. Theatre Design, Music. 1973 (Map-case 6)
  - The Britten Church Parables. Triptych. Theatre Design. 1973 (Map-case 6)
  - The Philanthropist. Goodman Theatre. Theatre Design. includes Henry IV. 1974 (Map-case 7)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades. Theatre Design, Music. 1974 (Map-case 7)
  - Hollywood Bowl Festival. Theatre Design, Music. 1974 (Map-case 7)
  - Hamlet. Theatre Design. 1974 (Map-case 7)
  - Henry IV Parts I & II, Theatre Design, wrinkled drawings. 1974 (Map-case 7)
  - Tanglewood Barn. Architectural. 1975 (Map-case 8)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades and Rug Concerts. Theatre Design, Music 1975 (Map-case 8)
  - Avery Fisher Hall. Renovation. Architectural. 1975 (Map-case 8)
  - Pittsburgh Public Theatre. Glass Menagerie. Cuckoo’s Nest. Theatre Design. 1975 (Map-case 8)
  - Hollywood Bowl. 1 of 2. Theatre Design. 1975 (Map-case 9)
  - Hollywood Bowl. 2 of 2. Theatre Design. 1975 (Map-case 9)
  - Les Troyens. Metropolitan Opera. New York. Theatre Design, Opera. 1 of 2. 1973, 1983 (Map-case 10)
  - Otello. Houston Grand Opera. Theatre Design, Opera. 1976 (Map-case 11)
  - Treats. Hudson Guild Theatre. Theatre Design. 1977 (Map-case 11)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades and Rug Concerts. Theatre Design, Music. 1977 (Map-case 11)
  - The Art Institute of Chicago. Theatre. Architectural. 1977 (Map-case 11)
  - Jockeys. Promenade Theatre New York. Theatre Design 1977 (Map-case 11)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute. Architectural. 1977 (Map-case 12)
  - Le Prophete. Metropolitan Opera. Theatre Design, Opera. 1977 (Map-case 12)
  - Henry V. Theatre Renovations. Pittsburgh Public Theatre. Theatre Design. 1977 (Map-case 12)
  - New York Cultural Amusement Center. Public Spaces. 1978 (Map-case 12)
  - Vojtech Blau Gallery. Public Spaces. 1 of 2. 1978 (Map-case 12)
  - A Broadway Musical. Riverside Church. 1 of 3. Theatre Design. 1978 (Map-case 13)
  - A Broadway Musical. Lunt-Fontaine Theatre. 2 of 3. Theatre Design. Photos, Photostats and logos. 1978 (Map-case 13)
  - A Broadway Musical. Lunt-Fontaine Theatre. 3 of 3. Theatre Design. B’way version. 1978 (Map-case 13)
  - Aquarius Theatre. Los Angeles. Architectural. binder broken. 1978 (Map-case 14)
  - Al Jolson Tonight. Theatre Design. Photos and xeroxes only. 1981 (Map-case 14)
  - Albert Herring. Theatre Design, Opera. 1981 (Map-case 14)
  - Garden Sculpture and Cafe for General Foods. Restaurant Design. George Lang Sculpture. 1981 (Oversize 14)
  - Lo Speziale. Queens College. Theatre Design, Opera. 1981 (Map-case 14)
  - Un Ballo in Maschera. Metropolitan Opera. Theatre Design. 1 of 2. 1977. drawings in poor condition. 1977 (Map-case 15)
  - Un Ballo in Maschera. Metropolitan Opera. Theatre Design. 2 of 2. 1977. drawings in poor condition. 1977 (Map-case 15)
  - Sanctuary. Theatre Design. 1978 (Map-case 16)
  - Vojtech Blau Gallery. Public Spaces. 2 of 2. 1978 (Map-case 16)
  - Mrs. Wexler Apartment. Public Spaces. 1979 (Map-case 16)
  - Warren Robertson Studio. Theatre Design 1979 (Map-case 16)
  - American Academy of Dramatic Art. Public Spaces. 1979 (Map-case 16)
  - Shapiro, Taxon, & Kopell Offices. Public Spaces. 1980 (Map-case 16)
  - Terra Nova. Center Theatre Group. Los Angeles. Theatre Design. 1978 (Map-case 17)
  - New York Philharmonic. Promenades. Theatre Design. 1978 (Map-case 17)
  - Royal Hunt of the Sun. Arizona Theatre Company. Theatre Design. 1978 (Map-case 17)
  - Citycorp Center. Public Spaces. 1980 (Map-case 18)
  - Pittsburgh Public Theatre. Terra Nova and Death of a Salesman. Theatre Design. 1980 (Map-case 18)
  - Taubman Company. People Wall. Public Spaces. 1981 (Map-case 18)
  - Taubman Company Airplane. Airplane Design. 1981 (Map-case 18)
  - Flag Hall. Smithsonian. Public Spaces, Museum Design. 1 of 2. 1982. drawings very poor condition. 1982 (Map-case 18)
  - Flag Hall. Smithsonian. Public Spaces, Museum Design. 2 of 2. 1982. drawings very poor condition. 1982 (Map-case 18)
  - Tanya Vanburg Apartment. Public Spaces. 1982 (Map-case 18)
  - Smithsonian. Elm Street. Public Spaces, Museum. 1 of 2. 1982 (Map-case 19)
  - Smithsonian. Elm Street. Public Spaces, Museum. 2 of 2. 1982 (Map-case 19)
  - Fiddler’s Green. Denver Symphony Orchestra. Theatre Design. 2 folders. 1983 (Map-case 20)
  - New York Philharmonic. Public Spaces, Board Room. 1983 (Map-case 20)
  - Holloran Hotel. Public Spaces. 1983 (Map-case 20)
  - Merril Lynch Corporate Televsion. Television Design. 1983 (Map-case 20)
  - Bershire Museum. Public Spaces. 1983 (Map-case 21)
  - LTV. Sculpture Display. Rodin Display. 1983 (Map-case 21)
  - Beale Street. Multi Media. 1983 (Map-case 21)
  - Denver Symphony Orchestra. Theatre Design. Performance Space. Rocky Mountain Music Festival. 1983 (Map-case 21)
  - Ninth Ave. Manganaros Hero Boy Restaurant. Public Spaces. 1983 (Map-case 22)
  - Health Club. Public Spaces. 1983 (Map-case 22)
  - Douglas Ellman. Public Spaces. 1983 (Map-case 22)
  - AIRCOA. Sheraton Denver Tech Center. Public Spaces. 1983 (Map-case 22)
  - AIRCOA. Sheraton Denver Tech Center. Public Spaces. 1983 (Map-case 23)
  - Plaza. Airport Inn. Public Spaces. 1983 (Map-case 23)
  - Higgins Inn. Worcester, MA. Public Spaces 1983 (Map-case 23)
  - Denver Symphony Orchestra. Theatre Design. 1 of 2. Performance Space. Fiddler’s Green. 1984 (Map-case 24)
  - Denver Symphony Orchestra. Theatre Design. 2 of 2. Performance Space. Fiddler’s Green. 1984 (Map-case 24)
  - Pepsi Commercial. Television Design. 1984 (Map-case 24)
  - Federal Hall. Public Spaces. 1984 (Map-case 24)
  - AIRCOA. St. Louis. Public Spaces. 1984 (Map-case 24)
  - AIRCOA. Brown Palace Hotel. Denver, Co., Public Spaces. 1984 (Map-case 24)
  - AIRCOA. Napa, CA. Public Spaces. 1984 (Map-case 24)
  - New York Philharmonic. Public Spaces. Traveling Exhibit. 1984 (Map-case 24)
  - AIRCOA. Colorado Springs. Public Spaces. 1985 (Map-case 25)
  - Squibb. Public Spaces. Lobby Design. 1985 (Map-case 25)
  - AIRCOA. Ontario, CA. Public Spaces. 1985 (Map-case 25)
  - AIRCOA. Missoula, Montana. Public Spaces. 1985 (Map-case 25)
  - Criswell Development CO. Public Spaces. 1 of 2. 1985 (Map-case 25)
  - Criswell Development CO. Public Spaces. 2 of 2. 1985 (Map-case 25)
  - AIRCOA. Denver Tech Center. Public Spaces. 1985 (Map-case 25)
  - Dallas Concert Hall. Public Spaces. 1984 (Map-case 26)
  - Trammel Crow Company. High Rise Sculptures. Public Spaces. 1984 (Map-case 26)
  - Trammel Crow Company. City Banner Scheme. Public Spaces. 1985 (Map-case 26)
  - LTV. Garage and Elevators. Trammel Crow Company. Public Spaces. 1985 (Map-case 27)
  - LTV Center Opening Night. Trammel Crow Company. Theatre Design. 1984 (Map-case 27)
  - LTV Center. Trammel Crow Company. Public Spaces. 1 of 2. 1984 (Map-case 28)
  - LTV Center. Trammel Crow Company. Public Spaces. 2 of 2. 1984 (Map-case 28)
  - LTV. Pavillion Christmas Tree. Trammel Crow Company. Public Spaces. 1985 (Map-case 28)
  - LTV Center Smithsonian Exhibit. Trammel Crow Company. Auxillary. 1984 (Map-case 29)
  - LTV Center Smithsonian Exhibit. Trammel Crow Company. Development. 1984 (Map-case 29)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Starfest. Theatre Design. 1980 (Map-case 30)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. S. Moss Park. Theatre Design. 1 of 2. Outdoor performance facility. 1981 (Map-case 31)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. S. Moss Park. Theatre Design. 2 of 2. Outdoor performance facility. 1981 (Map-case 31)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Market Center. Public Spaces. 1 of 2. 1984 (Map-case 31)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Market Center. Public Spaces. 2 of 2. 1984 (Map-case 31)
  - Dallas Symphony. Mort Meyerson Hall. Public Spaces. 1985 (Map-case 31)
  - Dallas Symphony Orchestra. Promenades and Rug Concerts. Public Spaces. 1985 (Map-case 31)
  - Dallas School System. Playground. Public Spaces. 1985 (Map-case 31)
  - LTV Center Information. Trammel Crow Company. Public Spaces. 1984 (Map-case 32)
  - LTV Center Outdoor Banners. Trammel Crow Company. Public Spaces. 1985 (Map-case 32)
  - New York Philharmonic. Avery Fisher Hall. Lincoln Center. Theatre Design Information. 1963-1978 (Map-case 32)
  - Center Theatre Group. Los Angeles. Theatre Design. Information. 1966-1996 (Map-case 32)
  - Liberties with Liberty. Public Spaces. 1986 (Map-case 33)
  - Horizons 86. Public Spaces. 1986 (Map-case 33)
  - Aaron Shapiro Offices. Public Spaces. 1986 (Map-case 33)
  - New York State Cultural Park. Public Spaces. 1986 (Map-case 33)
  - Hopeman Marine Architecture. Public Spaces. 1986 (Map-case 33)
  - Albany Urban Cultural Park. Public Spaces. 1986 (Map-case 34)
  - Poor Murderer. Bloomgarden. Theatre Design. Scenery and Light Design. 1976 (Map-case 35)
  - Sophisticated Ladies. Theatre Design. 1980 (Map-case 35)
  - Der Freischutz. New York City Opera. No Date. (Map-case 35)
  - Posters. You Can’t Take It With You, National Theatre. Sunday Times Guide to Shakespeare’s Characters. Gable and Harlow in Saratoga. (Map-case 35)
  - Godspell. Drawings. 1971 (Map-case 35)
  - Ellington. Theatre Design Music. 1987 (Map-case 36)
  - Salva. Theatre Design. 1987 (Map-case 36)
  - Terra Nova. Theatre Design. 1987 (Map-case 36)
  - Inforum. Public Spaces. 1987 (Map-case 36)
  - Barge. Public Spaces. 1988 (Map-case 36)
  - Rigolleto. Ballo. New York Grand Opera. Opera design. 1988 (Map-case 36)
  - Trans-Hudson Ferry. Side Loader. Public Spaces. 1986 (Map-case 37)
  - Trans-Hudson Ferry. End Loader. Public Spaces. 1986 (Map-case 37)
  - Trans-Hudson Ferry. End Loader. Public Spaces. 1987 (Map-case 37)
  - Trans-Hudson Ferry. Ferry III. Public Spaces. 1987 (Map-case 37)
  - Trans-Hudson Ferry. Black and White Sketches. Public Spaces. 1 of 3. 1987 (Map-case 37)
  - Trans-Hudson Ferry. Interior Sample Board. Public Spaces. 1987 (Map-case 37)
  - Trans-Hudson Ferry. Color Renderings. Incomplete. Public Spaces. 1 of 3. 1987 (Map-case 37)
  - Trans-Hudson Ferry. Color Renderings. Incomplete. Public Spaces. 2 of 3. 1987 (Map-case 37)
  - Trans-Hudson Ferry. Color Renderings. Incomplete. Public Spaces. 3 of 3. 1987 (Map-case 37)
  - Navy Pagent. Proposal. Theatre Design. 1986 (Map-case 38)
  - Navy Pagent Current. Theatre Design. 1986 (Map-case 38)
  - Navy Pagent. Background Drawings. Theatre Design. 1987 (Map-case 38)
  - Navy Pagent. Packs of Music. Theatre Design. 1 of 3. 1987 (Map-case 38)
  - Navy Pagent. Packs of Music. Theatre Design. 2 of 3. 1987 (Map-case 38)
  - Navy Pagent. Packs of Music. Theatre Design. 3 of 3. 1987 (Map-case 38)
  - Navy Pagent. Pack of Slide Mounts. Theatre Design. 3 of 3. 1987 (Map-case 38)
  - Navy Pagent. Screen Proportioner. Theatre Design. 1987 (Map-case 38)
  - Trans-Hudson Ferry. Black and White Sketches. Public Spaces. 2 of 3. 1987 (Map-case 38)
  - Trans-Hudson Ferry. Black and White Sketches. Public Spaces. 3 of 3. 1987 (Map-case 38)
  - Smithsonian Institute. USDA. Search for Life. Exhibit. Proposal. 1985 (Map-case 39)
  - Smithsonian Institute. USDA. Search for Life. Exhibit. Background. Early design. 1985 (Map-case 39)
  - Smithsonian Institute. USDA. Search for Life. Exhibit. Final Design. 1985 (Map-case 39)
  - Smithsonian Institute. USDA. Search for Life. Exhibit. Nmah Taylor Gallery. 1985 (Map-case 39)
  - Smithsonian Institute. USDA. Search for Life. Exhibit. Brochure Paste-Ups. Assorted artwork. 1987 (Map-case 40)
  - Hopeman Brothers. Canopy. 1987 (Map-case 41)
  - Central Park. Gonfalons. 1987 (Map-case 41)
  - SYDA Foundation. SYDA II. Fallsburgh, New York. 1989 (Map-case 41)
  - SYDA Foundation. Guru Mayi Birthday Celebration. Fallsburgh. New York. 1989 (Map-case 41)
  - Smithsonian Institute. USDA. Search for Life. Exhibit. Cold Spring Harbor Design. 1989 (Map-case 41)
  - Duplicate posters from various projects. (Map-case 41)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II. Brochures. Letterheads. Assorted Artwork. 1989 (Map-case 42)
  - We Are All In It Together. National Archives. World War II. Sketches. Plans. 1989 (Map-case 42)
  - Face to Face with Cardinal O’Connor. TV. 1989 (Map-case 42)
  - Matthew’s Company. 1991 (Map-case 43)
  - N. Glantz and Son. Exhibition Booth. 1991 (Map-case 43)
  - Library of Congress. Vatican Exhibition. 1991 (Map-case 43)
  - New York Theatre. Unfinished Stories. 1991 (Map-case 43)
  - Oxford Development Company. Mall. Public Spaces. 1990 (Map-case 44)
  - Oxford Development Company. Convention. 1990 (Map-case 44)
  - Photo Illusions. Booth. 1991 (Map-case 44)
  - Rathe Productions. Toys for Tots. 1991 (Map-case 44)
  - New York City Opera. Donor Recognition Sculpture. State Theatre. 1991 (Map-case 44)
  - Studio Christmas Cards. 1986-1988 (Map-case 45)
  - Studio I and II 277 West End Ave Building Plans. 1988 (Map-case 45)
  - Manganaro’s Hero Boy. 1983-1995 (Map-case 45)
  - St John the Devine Donor Banners. 1994 (Map-case 45)
  - St. John the Devine Exterior Lighting and Signage. 1994 (Map-case 45)
  - USTA Prudential A.V.I. Internet Kiosks. 1996 (Map-case 45)
  - Lifetime T.V. Attitudes. 1991 (Map-case 45)
  - B’way Theatre Institute Paine Webber. 1996 (Map-case 45)
  - American History Workshop- N.U.R.F.C. 1 of 2. 1998 (Map-case 46)
  - American History Workshop- N.U.R.F.C. 2 of 2. 1998 (Map-case 46)
  - ABC News Good Morning America. 1998 (Map-case 46)
  - ABC News 20/20 and World News Tonight. 1997-1998 (Map-case 46)
  - Judaica Museum- Presedential and Antique Dolls. 1997 (Map-case 46)
  - Judaica Museum- The 5th Commandment. 1997 (Map-case 46)
  - Judaica Museum- Pickles and Egg Cream/ Genizah. 1995-1996 (Map-case 46)
  - NSO Kennedy Center Summer Festival. 1988-1989 (Map-case 46)
  - The Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL. In the Parks. 1991 (Map-case 47)
  - The Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL. In the Parks. #3, 1 of 3. 1989 (Map-case 47)
  - The Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL. In the Parks. #3, 2 of 3. 1989 (Map-case 47)
  - The Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL. In the Parks. #3, 3 of 3. 1989 (Map-case 47)
  - The Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL. In the Parks. #2. 1986 (Map-case 47)
  - The Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL. In the Parks. #1, 1 of 2. 1982 (Map-case 47)
  - The Carlos Moseley Pavilion MET/PHIL. In the Parks. #1, 2 of 2. 1982 (Map-case 47)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan- Lighting. 1997 (Map-case 48)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan-Concert Lighting and Wiring. 1996 (Map-case 48)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan- Rigging. 1996 (Map-case 48)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan Implementation. 1995 (Map-case 48)
  - BSO Pops Spring. 1998 (Map-case 49)
  - BSO Pops Spring. 1997 (Map-case 49)
  - BSO Pops Winter. 1995 (Map-case 49)
  - BSO Pops Summer. 1995 (Map-case 49)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan- CAD Survey. 1996 (Map-case 49)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan- Survey. 1995 (Map-case 49)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan-Survey Background. 1995 (Map-case 49)
  - BSO Systems Update Plan-Study Plan. (Map-case 49)
  - Calgary Philharmonic. 1995 (Map-case 50)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1995 (Map-case 50)
  - New York Grand Opera-Viva Verdi. 1995 (Map-case 50)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1994 (Map-case 50)
  - New York Grand Opera- Viva Verdi. 1994 (Map-case 50)
  - New York Grand Opera Festival. 1991 (Map-case 50)
  - Nextstage Entertainment Corp. Dallas Theatre Consulting. 1998 (Map-case 51)
  - Shubert Ticketing Services. 1999 (Map-case 51)
  - Nextstage Entertainment Corp. Dallas Theatre ID/Iconography. 1998-1999 (Map-case 51)
  - Nextstage Entertainment Corp. Pinicchio. 1999-2000 (Map-case 51)
  - Nextstage Entertainment Corp. Dallas Theatre Consulting II. 2000 (Map-case 51)
  - Florida 2012. 2000 (Map-case 51)
  - High Altitude. 2001 (Map-case 51)
  - Boyington Field LLC. 2003 (Map-case 52)
  - 277 W.E.A Building Plans Elevator Terrace. 2003 (Map-case 52)
  - Studio II Fabrication. 1984-1989 (Map-case 52)
  - 277 W.E.A. Apartment 16A. (Map-case 52)
  - The Battery. 2002-2003 (Map-case 52)
  - Creative Projects. Graphics. 2001-2003 (Map-case 52)
  - Past Projects. Posters. (Map-case 52)
  - Photography. Large Format. (Map-case 52)
  - ABC News World News Tonight. 1989 (Map-case 52)
  - Schnitzer Hall. 2004 (Map-case 52)
  - Detroit Jaffe Symphony Hall. Conceptual Design and Research. 2002 (Map-case 53)
  - Campus Maritus. Graphic Images, Park Lighting, Set Plans. 2002 (Map-case 53)
  - Jaffe Midland. Center for the Arts. 2002 (Map-case 54)
  - Design. 2002 (Map-case 54)
  - Theatre Information. 2002 (Map-case 54)
  - Lighting. 2002 (Map-case 54)
  - Shell. 2002 (Map-case 54)
  - CAD Drafting. 2002 (Map-case 54)
  - Preliminary Work/Research. 2002 (Map-case 54)
  - The Talking Cure. 2004 (Map-case 54)
- Models., Series: III
  This series is not available for public viewing.